let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What was Mickey Mouse's original name?",
        answer: "Morimer Mouse",
        options: [
            "Morimer Mouse",
            "The Rat",
            "Marvin Mouse",
            "Marshall Mouse"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which superhero has the alter ego Wade Wilson?",
        answer: "Deadpool",
        options: [
            "Black Panther",
            "Deadpool",
            "Ant-Man",
            "Hawk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who sings Poker Face?",
        answer: "Lady Gaga",
        options: [
            "Kelly Clarkston",
            "Taylor Swift",
            "Madonna",
            "Lady Gaga"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How would Groot answer this question?",
        answer: "I am groot",
        options: [
            "Mark is the bomb yo!",
            "Groot I am young padawan",
            "I am groot",
            "YO homie whats up!"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Stark Industries is owned by who?",
        answer: "Iron Man",
        options: [
            "Hulk",
            "Iron Fist",
            "Captain America",
            "Iron Man"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The Sword In The Stone is called?",
        answer: "Excalibur",
        options: [
            "Excalibur",
            "Nibue",
            "Callandor",
            "Glamdring"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "This Museum Is In Night at the Museum?",
        answer: "Museum of Natural History",
        options: [
            "National Museum of the American Indian",
            "The Smithsonian",
            "Museum of Natural History",
            "The Louvre"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Logan is usually known by the hero name?",
        answer: "Woleverine",
        options: [
            "Aquaman",
            "Woleverine",
            "Green Lantern",
            "Silver Surfer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Who sings the song Blurred Lines?",
        answer: "Robin Thicke",
        options: [
            "Pharrell Williams",
            "Nick Cannon",
            "Pitbull",
            "Robin Thicke"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Playstation was developed by?",
        answer: "Sony",
        options: [
            "Capcom",
            "Woleverine",
            "Sony",
            "Sega"
        ]
    }

];